<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work on A Byte of Cybersecurity</title><link>https://lloydlore.github.io/tags/work/</link><description>Recent content in Work on A Byte of Cybersecurity</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lloydlore.github.io/tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>:"Mono font for Chinese and English in vscode"</title><link>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/mono-font-in-vscode/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/mono-font-in-vscode/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="abstract"&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This document provides a solution for configuring VSCode to use monospace fonts where Chinese (CJK) characters occupy exactly twice the width of English characters, ensuring proper alignment in mixed-language text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When working with mixed Chinese and English text in VSCode, proper character alignment is crucial for code comments, documentation, and text formatting. True monospace fonts should maintain a 2:1 width ratio between full-width CJK characters and half-width Latin characters.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Playing Game with Myself</title><link>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/playing-games-with-myself/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/playing-games-with-myself/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="no-games-for-a-long-time"&gt;No Games for a Long Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am obssessed with digital games since I was 5 years old. That means I&amp;rsquo;ve already played games over the past 30 years. Now I have a 9 years old son, I sometimes watch him playing his favorate games. To be honest, I am so envy on him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have to work, work, and work. When I finally got sometime, I just unlock my cellphone, swiping the glass. No, that&amp;rsquo;s not a gamer. A gamer should sit down or sink down the coach, holding his controller, and playing the game from day to night. That is me, that&amp;rsquo;s the devotion I am always seeking for.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CNAS 和 CMA 认定</title><link>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/cnas_and_cma_accreditation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lloydlore.github.io/posts/cnas_and_cma_accreditation/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;这两年中国汽车行业里对网络安全的认证需求越来越多，同时要求也越来越高。我能够观察
到，随着中国电动汽车的倾销加剧，各国对中国生产的电动汽车的门槛，也会随之升高。&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>